newsoftwarelab.com 2009-06-04

# Privacy

**Overview**  
At Authorised Software Reseller, we are concerned about your online privacy. we've created our privacy policy to demonstrate how we protect the privacy of our customers. our company studies online customer activity and collects different information about our customers in order to provide you with the finest product selection and shopping experience. this document should explain the following regarding the use of our site 

**What kind of information do we collect from you?**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide our visitors and customers with a superior customized online experience. when you browse and shop on our site, we collect two types of information about our visitors: personal information and non-personally identifiable information. 

**Personal information**  
Personal information is requested when you place an order. we need to know your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, and product details to process your order and to notify you of your order status. 

**Non-personally identifiable information**  
This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. the information of this kind may include the url you came from, ip address, domain types (e.g. .com or .org, etc.), your browser type, the country, state and telephone area code where your server is located, the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit, the advertisements you clicked. we use this information for enhancing the operation of our site, serving advertisements, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. 

**How do we use the information we collect?**   
We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. the information provided to us as a result of your online purchase such as your gender, name, e-mail address, phone number(s) and shipping address is used only to send orders, to inform you of your order status and sending our company newsletter and promotional information. this information is completely confidential and will not be disclosed or sold to any other party. we may also use non-personally identifiable information about our web site visitors such as url you came from, ip address, domain types, your browser type, the country, the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit, the advertisements you clicked. we use this information for enhancing the operation of our site, serving advertisements, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. 

**Secure ordering**  
Our site was developed to support secure online purchasing through secure socket layer (ssl) technology. all information that you provide during the shopping process is encrypted for your protection. you'll know that you're in an encrypted area when you see a solid key when using netscape navigator or a closed lock when using internet explorer. when you place your order online, your personal information will be encrypted and transmitted via a secured connection. your credit card details are not available for us and used only to process your order online. 

**Cookies**  
We use cookies in the operation of our site at the moment. privacy policy changes if we will make changes to any terms or conditions of the privacy policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather and how we might use it. if at any point we decide to use the information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail. you will have a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. we will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
